clipshack.com 2010-11-20

# _

_Effective June 8, 2006_

**_ClipShack Privacy Policy_**

Reality Digital, Inc. (“ ** _Reality Digital_** ”) provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information received from users of its website [www.clipshack.com](http://www.clipshack.com/) (this “ ** _Site_** ”).  This Privacy Policy applies only to this Site and is incorporated into the Clipshack.com Terms of Use Agreement. 

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time.  We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site.  Please consult the Site regularly for any changes. 

By using our Site you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us, which means the use of such information as set forth herein, including but not limited to collecting, storing and deleting, using, combining, disclosing information and transferring it internationally.     

**Information Collection and Use**

Our primary goals in collecting information are to provide and improve our services, features and content, to administer your ClipShack Membership (together, the “ ** _Service_** ”), and to enable users to enjoy and easily navigate the Site.

__Personally Identifiable Information__ _._  

o        When you register with us through the Site to become a “ ** _ClipShack Member_** ,” we may  collect personally identifiable information, including, but not limited to, name, email address, postal address, IP address, account user name and password (“ ** _Personal Information_** ”). Personal Information is information about you that when on its own or in combination with other identifiers can be used to contact or identify you.  We use your Personal Information to provide the Service, facilitate your use of the Site and respond to your inquiries. 

o        We also collect the non-personally identifiable information that you provide as part of registration ( _e.g._ , without limitation, zip code, age, gender, and your interests) (“ ** _Anonymous Demographic Information_** ”).  We may combine your Personal Information with this Anonymous Demographic Information or with aggregate information collected from other Reality Digital users to attempt to provide you with a better experience and improve the quality and value of the Service. 

o        We may also use your Personal Information to send you Reality Digital newsletters, promotional materials about other products or services and other information that may be of interest to you ( _e.g.,_ business partner recommendations as described in the Terms of Use).  Where you agree to the terms and conditions of Reality Digital Terms of Use you are given the opportunity to opt-in to the receipt of such information from us in the future.  If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such information from us, you may follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in the communication or you may also update your registration preferences information. (See “ **Changing or Deleting Information,** ” below.) 

__Log Data__ _.   _When you visit the Site, whether as a ClipShack Member or a non-registered user just browsing, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website ( ** _“Log Data”_** ).  This Log Data may include information such as your   browser type and the domain from which you are visiting.  We do not use this information to identify you personally.  We use it to monitor use of the Site and the Service and for the Site’s technical administration. 

**Cookies**

Like many websites, we use “cookies” to collect information.  A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk for record-keeping purposes.  We use cookies for two purposes.  First, we utilize persistent cookies to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to the Site.  Second, we utilize session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Site, to better understand how you interact with the Site, and to monitor aggregate usage by users and web traffic routing on the Site.  Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you disconnect from the Site and Service.  Third party advertisers on the Site may also place or read cookies on your browser.  You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit.  If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all functionality of the Service. You can learn more about the use of cookies by visiting [http://networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/ "http://networkadvertising.org/") or <http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/HTTP_cookie.>

**ClipShack Friends**

You may be interested in inviting your friends to become ClipShack Members.  You can do so by visiting our “Invite” webpage where you have the option of adding one or more e-mail addresses into an online form.  A message will be sent from ClipShack on your behalf inviting your friend to become a Clipshack Member. Reality Digital will only use this email address for the purpose of sending this “Invite a Friend” email and for no other purpose, unless the invitee becomes a member of ClipShack.  These email addresses will be stored in the ClipShack address book that you create.    

**Phishing**

We do not and will not, at any time, request your credit card information, your Reality Digital ID, login password, or national identification numbers in a non-secure or unsolicited e-mail or telephone communication.

Identity theft and the practice currently known as "phishing" are of great concern to Reality Digital. Safeguarding information to help protect you from identity theft is our priority. For more information about phishing, you may want to visit the Federal Trade Commission’s website at <http://www.ftc.gov/bcp/conline/pubs/alerts/phishingalrt.htm.>

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

_ClipShack Members_.  When you register through the Site and upload your video and film clips (“ ** _Clips_** ”) to the Site, you can decide who you want to have access to your Clips. By default, your Clips are marked “ ** _Private_** ,” which means only you as a ClipShack Member can see the Clips you have posted.  If you want to extend viewing privileges to your friends, you can edit the “Access Settings” on the Properties page for that Clip and invite your friends to become ClipShack Members and as such they will be able to see your Clips like other ClipShack Members.  If you want general website visitors to see your Clips, you can select the “ ** _Public_** ” setting in the Properties page.  Please note that if you choose the Public option for sharing your Clips, you will be sharing your posted content and any Personal Information included therein with the public.  Providing your Personal Information and any other information about you, in or associated with the Clip, is voluntary and should correlate with the degree of interaction you want to have with others. 

_Reality Digital Affiliated Entities_ : Your Clips may be included on the websites of Reality Digital’s affiliates, distribution partners or third-party service providers as described further in our Terms of Use.  If you do not want your Clips shared with such entities please do not become a ClipShack Member.

__Anonymous Information__.  We may share Anonymous Demographic Information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis and demographic profiling.  This information will not contain your Personal Information. 

__Service Providers__.  We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service, to provide the Service on our behalf or to perform Site-related services ( _e.g._ , without limitation, maintenance services, database management and improvement of the Site’s features).  These third parties have access to your Personal Information only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to use it for any other purpose.

__Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement__.  Reality Digital cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law.  We may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Reality Digital or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity. 

__Business Transfers__.  Reality Digital may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including information provided by you, in connection with a merger, reorganization, or sale of assets, or in the event of bankruptcy.  If the new entity wishes to make additional uses of your information different from those described in this Privacy Policy you will have the opportunity to decline such use at that time.

**Changing or Deleting Your Information**

All ClipShack Members may review, update, correct or delete the Personal Information in their registration profile.  If you completely delete any such information, then your account may become deactivated.  If you would like us to delete your record in our system, please contact us and we will attempt to accommodate your request.  See below for privacy contact information. 

**Security & International Transfer **

Reality Digital is very concerned with safeguarding your information.  We employ administrative, physical and electronic measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access.  Your information may be transferred to—and maintained on—computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction.  Reality Digital transfers Personal Information to the United States and maintains and processes it there and you consent to such transfer. 

**Links to Other Sites**

_  
_ Our Site may contain links to other websites. We may also use third-party advertising companies to serve or track advertisements on our Site and other websites.  These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to measure advertising effectiveness and to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you.  If you choose to visit an advertiser by “clicking on” a banner ad or other type of advertisement, you will be directed to that third party’s website.  The fact that we link to a website or present a banner ad or other type of advertisement is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party.  We do not exercise control over third party websites.  These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you.  This Privacy Policy addresses the use and disclosure of information that we collect from you through this Site.  Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit to them.  We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit. 

**Our Policy Toward Children**

_  
_ This Site is not directed to persons under 18.  If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at help via http://www.clipshack.com/contact.aspx. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at http://www.clipshack.com/contact.aspx or at: **Reality Digital, 600 Townsend Street, Suite 170e, San Francisco, CA   94103.**

© 2006 Reality Digital, Inc.
